All right, now that you've had a chance to fill this notebook out yourself,
你已经自己填写了此 notebook
let's go through and take a look at my solutions.
下面看看我的答案
I have already run all of the data downloading and processing steps,
我已经运行了所有的数据下载和处理步骤
so we can start right away here at step four,
可以直接从第 4 步开始
where we start adding our own code.
从这步开始需要添加代码
First things first, let's split our training dataset into a training and validation set.
首先 将训练集拆分成训练和验证集
Here we have 25,000 reviews and we've already randomize the order of the reviews.
我们有 25,000 条影评 已经随机化排列影评
So, to split into a training and validation set,
为了拆分出训练集和验证集
we can just take the first 10,000 as
我们将前 10,000 条作为验证集
the validation set and then leave the remaining as the training set.
并将剩下的作为训练集
Once we've done that, as we did in the Boston Housing notebook,
然后就像在 Boston Housing notebook 中一样
saved the testing, validation,
将测试集 验证集和训练集
and training datasets to CSV files in an appropriately chosen data directory.
保存到 csv 文件中并放到指定的 /data 目录下
Also like in the Boston Housing dataset,
并且和 Boston Housing 数据集一样
we make sure that when we save the CSV files we do not include a header or an index
在保存 csv 文件时 不要包含标题或索引
as that is the format that SageMaker requires the data files to be in.
因为 SageMaker 要求数据文件是这样的格式
Now, that the test validation and training sets have been saved,
保存好测试 验证和训练集后
we can first do a little bit of memory management.
先管理下内存
So, you will see this sort of a code tail
你将在很多 notebook 中
appear in a number of the notebooks and the reason for this is that
看到这种代码 原因是
the default virtual machine that our notebook instance is running
Notebook 实例运行所在的默认虚拟机
inside of doesn't have a lot of RAM available to it.
没有太多的内存
So, if we let unused data just sort of linger,
如果我们只是让不使用的数据留在那
we can accidentally run out of memory inside of the notebook.
可能会在 notebook 中耗尽内存
So, we have two options.
有两种解决方案
We could increase the capabilities of
我们可以增加
the virtual machine that our notebook is running inside of,
notebook 所在的虚拟机的内存
but that may be costly,
但是这样会带来成本
or we could do something like this where we make sure to keep
或者可以这样跟踪内存
track of memory that is no longer being used and free it.
并且释放不再使用的内存
Next step is to upload the data files to S3.
下一步是将数据文件上传到 S3
This is essentially done in the same way as we did in the Boston Housing and notebook.
方法和在 Boston Housing notebook 中一样
The difference really is that we are changing the prefix.
唯一的区别是更改 prefix
Remember the prefix is basically like the folder name on some drive,
prefix 相当于在某个驱动器上的文件夹名称
and the drive is the default drive or bucket that corresponds to this notebook.
该驱动器是此 notebook 对应的默认驱动器或存储桶
Aside from that, we just use the upload data method for
然后 使用 upload_data 方法
each of our data files and upload them to S3.
将每个数据文件上传到 S3
Now, the data files have been uploaded and we can move on.
上传了数据文件后 继续下一步
To begin with, we make sure to get hold of the execution role.
首先获取执行角色
Remember that the role describes what other resources our notebook has
角色描述了 notebook 可以访问的其他资源
access to and we need to make sure to give the estimator we're about to create a role.
我们需要为要创建的 estimator 提供一个角色
We may as well give it the same role that we're using for this notebook.
我们可以提供与此 notebook 一样的角色
We also need to make sure to create the image URI for
还需要为 XGBoost 算法创建镜像 URI
the XGBoost algorithm and that depends on the region that we're currently using.
取决于当前使用的区域
So, we use the get image URI method.
我们使用 get_image_uri 方法
Then, we create the SageMaker estimator objects
然后像在 Boston Housing notebook 中一样
in the exact same way as we did in the Boston Housing notebook.
创建 SageMaker estimator 对象
The difference here is in one of the XGB hyperparameters.
区别在于其中一个 XGBoost 超参数
Since we are trying to determine sentiment that is
因为我们要判断情感
a binary outcome, positive or negative,
情感结果是二元的正面或负面情感
we want to make sure that we're using a binary or a two-outcome regression,
所以需要使用二元回归
and in particular, logistic regression is typically what we want to be using.
我们通常使用逻辑回归
So, the only real difference between the Boston Housing notebook and this one is
Boston Housing notebook 与此 notebook 的真正唯一区别是
that we have changed the objective to being a binary logistic regression.
我们将这里的 objective 改成了二元逻辑回归
Okay. So, now we have defined the XGBoost model and we need to actually feed it.
Ok定义了 XGBoost 模型后 我们需要拟合该模型
So, again just like in the Boston Housing notebook,
就像在 Boston Housing notebook 中一样
we just provide the training and validation datasets and away it goes.
我们只需提供训练集和验证集就可以了
Once the model has been fed,
拟合模型后
we can go on to testing to see how well our model behaves.
我们可以测试模型 看看模型的效果
First thing we need to do, is create a new transformer object.
首先需要新建一个 transformer 对象
Once that's been done we setup
创建完毕后 设置转换作业
a transform job making sure to specify both where the test data is,
需要指定测试数据的位置
the type of data it is,
数据类型
and the way in which SageMaker could if necessary, split the data up.
以及有必要的话 指定 SageMaker 拆分数据的方式
Now, remember the transform job is happening in the background,
注意 转换作业
is being set up and run in the background.
会在后台运行
So, if we use the weight method we can get some visual output to let us
我们可以使用 wait() 方法直观地看看
know how that transform job is progressing and when it's finished.
转换作业的进展以及何时运行完毕
Once the transform job has finished up,
转换作业运行完毕后
we can copy the output from that transform job to the notebook instance.
我们可以将转换作业的输出复制到 notebook 实例中
Then, reading that data and check to see how well our model perform.
然后读取数据 看看模型的表现
Well, not so bad, almost 87 percent.
不太糟糕 准确率几乎达到 87%
Again, we can then do the optional cleanup step,
我们可以选择完成清理步骤
to get rid of any of the files that we created throughout the notebook. So, that's it.
删除在整个 notebook 中创建的所有文件搞定
You have created your first ever model in SageMaker.
你在 SageMaker 中创建了你的首个模型
Of course, we have used a lot of
当然 我们使用了
the high-level functionality of SageMaker and as a result,
很多 SageMaker 高阶功能
most of the magic has happened in the background.
所以大部分工作都在后台完成了
In the next few videos, we're going to go into
在接下来的几个视频中
much more detail as to how SageMaker works.
我们将非常详细地了解 SageMaker 的运行原理